A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch Slide Collection, 1967-1993
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Gunston Hall Gardens, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B31
- Gunston Hall School House, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B32
- Hope Park House Seen From Nike Site, Fairfax, VA, 1973 November; Hope-Park-B2
- Hope Park House Exterior, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-B3
- North Eastward View From House, Fairfax, VA, 1973 November; Hope-Park-B4
- Southward View From House, Fairfax, VA, 1973 November; Hope-Park-B5
- Westward View From House, Fairfax, VA, 1973 November; Hope-Park-B6
- Southward View From House, Fairfax, VA, 1973 November; Hope-Park-B7
- Drawing of Mill (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B8
- Robey's Mill (c. 1930)/ Hope Park, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B9
- Mill Interior- Hope Park Mill, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B10
- Robey's Mill (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B11
- Robey's Mill (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B12
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B13
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B14
- Hope Park Mill, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B15
- Mill Race, Hope Park Mill (1938), Fairfax, VA, Undated; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B16
- Hope Park Millers House from South, Fairfax, VA, 1973 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B17
- Miller's House (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B18
- Hope Park Mill Millers House, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B19
- Millers House (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B20
- Tenant House Robey's Mill, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B21
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B22
- Tentant House at Hope Park Mill, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B23
- Sprinf House at Robey's Mill (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B24
- Robey's Mill Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B25
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B26
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B27
- Millers House (Hope Park), Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B28
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B29
- Slave Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1980 October; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B30
- Robey's Mill District Fairfax County, Fairfax, VA, 1990 November; Hope-Park-Robey's-Mill-B31
- Huntley Out Building, Alexandria, VA, 1979; Huntley-B1
- Huntley Out Building, Alexandria, VA, 1979; Huntley-B2
- Huntlry Mansion, Alexandria, VA, 1980; Huntley-B3
- Huntley - Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B4
- Huntley - Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B8
- Huntley - Rear Facade, Alexandria, VA, 1975 April; Huntley-B9
- Huntley - Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B10
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B11
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, 1988 Fall; Huntley-B12
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B13
- Huntley District Fairfax County, Alexandria, VA, 1990 December; Huntley-B14
- Huntley - N.E. View, Alexandria, VA, 1989 November; Huntley-B15
- View from SE Corner Harrison Lane and Polins Court, Alexandria, VA, 1989 November; Huntley-B16
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B17
- Huntley Tenant House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B18
- View To Huntley from Polins Court, Alexandria, VA, 1989 November; Huntley-B19
- View To House From Church Parking Lot, Alexandria, VA, 1989 November; Huntley-B21
- Huntley Tenant House, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B22
- Huntley Mansion Tentant House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B23
- Huntley Tentant House, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B24
- Huntley Mansion Necessary, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B25
- Huntley - Privy, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B26
- Huntley Mansion Necessary, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B27
- Huntley Mansion Necessary, Alexandria, VA, 1979 October; Huntley-B28
- Huntley Mansion Necessary, Alexandria, VA, 1979 October; Huntley-B29
- Huntley - Outbuilding Privy, Alexandria, VA, 1980 January; Huntley-B30
- Privy, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B31
- Huntley Mansion Entrance to Root Cellar and Ice House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B32
- Huntley Ice House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B33
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B34
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B35
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, 1979 October; Huntley-B36
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B37
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, 1988 Fall; Huntley-B38
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B39
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B40
- Huntley Outbuilding, Alexandria, VA, 1979 October; Huntley-B41
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B42
- Huntley Dependency, Alexandria, VA, 1979 August; Huntley-B43
- Huntley Dependancy, Alexandria, VA, 1988 Fall; Huntley-B44
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B45
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B46
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B47
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B47
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B49
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B50
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B51
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B52
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B53
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B54
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B55
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B56
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B57
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B58
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B59
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B60
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B61
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B62
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B63
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B64
- Huntley Interior, Alexandria, VA, 1980 November; Huntley-B65
- Huntley, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Huntley-B66
- Hutchison House Exterior, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Hutchison-B1
- Hutchison House Exterior View, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Hutchison-B3
- Hutchison House Exterior View, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Hutchison-B4
- Hutchison House Interior, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Hutchison-B5
- Hutchison House Interior, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Hutchison-B6
- House, Southeast corner of Hurst Street and Idylwood Road [converted country store], Idylwood, VA, Undated; Idylwood-B1
- House, Idylwood, Idylwood, VA, Undated; Idylwood-B2
- House, Idylwood, Idylwood, VA, Undated; Idylwood-B3
- Jackson-House House Exterior View, McLean, VA, 1988; Jackson-House-B1
- Jackson-House House Exterior View, McLean, VA, Undated; Jackson-House-B2
- Jackson-House House Exterior View, McLean, VA, 1988; Jackson-House-B4
- Jackson-House House Exterior View, McLean, VA, 1988; Jackson-House-B5
- Jackson-House House Exterior View, McLean, VA, 1989 October; Jackson-House-B6
- Jackson-House House Exterior View, McLean, VA, 1989 October; Jackson-House-B7
- Jackson House Exterior- 1988, McLean, VA, 1988 September; Jackson-House-B8
- Jackson House Exterior- 1988, McLean, VA, 1988 September; Jackson-House-B9
- Cabin on Jackson House Property, McLean, VA, 1989 October; Jackson-House-B10
- Log Cabin- Jackson House Property, McLean, VA, 1989 October; Jackson-House-B11
- Jackson House Cabin, McLean, VA, 1988 September; Jackson-House-B12
- Jackson House, McLean, VA, 1989 October; Jackson-House-B13
- Jackson House, McLean, VA, Undated; Jackson-House-B14
- Ft. Buffalo Primary Election Day, Falls Church, VA, 1988; James-Lee-School-B1
- Ft. Buffalo Primary Election Day, Falls Church, VA, 1988; James-Lee-School-B2
- Ft. Buffalo Primary Election Day, Falls Church, VA, 1988; James-Lee-School-B3
- James Lee Faculity c.1950, Falls Church, VA, Undated; James-Lee-School-B5
- James Lee Faculity c.1950, Falls Church, VA, Undated; James-Lee-School-B6
- Reston, VA - Lake Anne, Reston, VA, 1972; LAKA-B3
- Lake Anne, Reston, VA, 1980 January; LAKA-B14
- Langley Meeting House Sign, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B4
- Langley Meeting House, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B5
- Langley Friends Meeting House, Langley, VA, 1980 June; Langley-B6
- Langley- Friends Meeting House Buttresses, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B8
- Friends Meeting House Butteresses, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B9
- Haying At Langley, 1919, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B10
- New Development In Langley Area, Langley, VA, 1980 June; Langley-B11
- Langley Meeting House, Langley, VA, 1980 June; Langley-B12
- Gunnell's Chapel, Langley, VA, 1980 June; Langley-B15
- Langley Meeting House, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B16
- Hickory Hill, Langley, VA, 1980 June; Langley-B17
- Open space North side of Pike approaching fork, Langley, VA, 1980 June; Langley-B18
- Balls Hill Road and Old Dominion Drive, Langley, VA, Undated; Langley-B19
- Grave Stone, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B2
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B4
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B5
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B7
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B8
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B9
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B10
- Laurel Hill, Lorton, VA, 1992 October; Laurel-Hill-B11
- Leeton Barn (Dairy), Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B1
- Leeton Barn, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B2
- Leeton Corncrib, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B3
- Leeton Corncrib, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B4
- Development Encroaching, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B5
- Development Encroaching, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B6
- Leeton Shed, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B7
- Leeton Barn Silo, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B8
- Leeton Barns and Outbuildings, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B9
- Leeton Shed, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B10
- Leeton Corncrib, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B11
- Leeton Barns and Outbuildings, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B12
- Development Encroaching, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B13
- Leeton Dairy Barn (interior), Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B14
- Leeton Shed, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Leeton-B15
- Legato School Relocated, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Legato-School-B1
- Legato School Relocated, Fairfax, VA, 1974; Legato-School-B2
- Legato School Relocated, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Legato-School-B3
- Legato School Relocated, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Legato-School-B4
- Legato School Relocated, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Legato-School-B5
- Outbuildings at Level Green, Centreville, VA, 1979 August; Level-Green-B1
- Catholic Chapel Near Level Green, Centreville, VA, 1979 August; Level-Green-B2
- Lewinsville, Lewinsville, VA, 1985 April; Lewinsville-B1
- Lewinsville Post Office, Lewinsville, VA, Undated; Lewinsville-B3
- Lewinsville Post Office, Lewinsville, VA, Undated; Lewinsville-B4
- Jones Tombstone- Lewinsville, Lewinsville, VA, Undated; Lewinsville-B5
- Jones Tombstone- Lewinsville, Lewinsville, VA, Undated; Lewinsville-B6
- Jones Tombstone- Lewinsville, Lewinsville, VA, Undated; Lewinsville-B7
- Sears House, McLean, VA, Undated; McLean-B2
- Sears House, McLean, VA, Undated; McLean-B3
- Merry Hill, McLean, VA, Undated; McLean-B4
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B1
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B2
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B3
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B4
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B5
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B6
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B7
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B8
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B9
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B10
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B11
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B12
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B13
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B14
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B15
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B16
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B17
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B18
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B19
- The Gables of McLean - Terri Knowl Court, Parlour Homes Inc., McLean, VA, 1988; McLean-Parlour-Homes-B20
- Middleton Farm House, 1985; Middleton-B1
- Middleton Farm 1st House, 1985; Middleton-B3
- Mitchell-Weeks Outbuilding, Chantilly, VA, 1991; Mitchell-Weeks-B2
- Mitchell-Weeks Outbuilding, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Mitchell-Weeks-B3
- Mitchell's Tavern front exterior, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Mitchell-Weeks-B4
- Mount Air District, Lorton, VA, 1990 December; Mt.Air-B5
- Mount Air, Lorton, VA, Undated; Mt.Air-B6
- Mount Air Outbuliding, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B7
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B8
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B9
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B10
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B11
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B12
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B14
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B16
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B17
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B18
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B20
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B21
- Mount Air Ruins, Lorton, VA, 1992 May 20; Mt.Air-B22
- Mount Air, Lorton, VA, Undated; Mt.Air-B23
- Mount Pleasant Baptist Church, Herndon, VA, Undated; Mt.Pleasant-B1
- Carriage Enterance, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B1
- Carriage Enterance, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B3
- River Entrance Before The Civil War c. 1850, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B6
- Mount Vernon Exterior, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B8
- Mount Vernon Gardens, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B9
- Mount Vernon Gardens, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B10
- Mount Vernon Hall, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B12
- Mount Vernon Hall, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B13
- Central Hall, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B14
- Aerial View, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B17
- West Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B20
- Small Dining Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B23
- South Hall-Large Dining Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B24
- Large Dining Rm. (South Hall), Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B25
- Family Kitchen, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B28
- Mount Vernon Kitchen Interior, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B29
- Evolution of Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B32
- Evolution of Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B33
- Washington's Birth Place, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B35
- Sarcophagus at Tomb of General Washington, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B37
- Tomb Guard, Mount Vernon, VA, 1980 February; Mt.Vernon-B38
- The Powell Coach, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B39
- Washington Family Savage Portrait, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B42
- Potowmack Canal Wagley Diorama, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B44
- Potowmack Canal Wagley Diorama, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B45
- Potowmack Canal Wagley Diorama, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B46
- George Washington, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B47
- Mount Vernon - 1861, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B48
- Tea Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B49
- Tea Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B50
- Tea Room, Mount Vernon Trolley Station c. 1930, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B51
- Washington Grist Mill - 1735, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B52
- Mt.Vernon Garden, Mount Vernon, VA, 1980 February; Mt.Vernon-B53
- Reconstructed Greenhouse and Servents' Quarters, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B54
- Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B55
- Evolution of Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B56
- Mount Vernon Cental Hall, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B57
- Washington's Secretary Desk and Chair in Study, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B59
- Washington's Secretary Desk and Chair in Study, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B60
- Front Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B61
- Front Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B62
- Front Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B63
- The Scullery In The Family Kitchen, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B64
- The Scullery In The Family Kitchen, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B65
- The Scullery In The Family Kitchen, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B66
- George and Matha Washington's Bed Room (Current), Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B67
- George and Matha Washington's Bed Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B69
- The Little Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B70
- The Little Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B71
- The Little Parlor, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B72
- Large Dining Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B73
- Large Dining Room (South Hall), Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B74
- Detail Of Marbel Mantle and Garniture, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B75
- Detail Of Marbel Mantle and Garniture, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B76
- Detail Of Marbel Mantle and Garniture, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B77
- The Family Kitchen Original Fireplace, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B78
- The Family Kitchen Original Fireplace, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B79
- Small Dining Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B80
- Small Dining Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B81
- Evolution of Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, 1976 November; Mt.Vernon-B83
- Mt.Vernon High School, Mount Vernon, VA, 1988 Fall; Mt.Vernon-B84
- Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B85
- Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B88
- Carriage Entrance at Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B89
- George Washington's Grist Mill Built 1735, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B90
- Washington Family Portrait (Savage), Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B91
- Mount Vernon Gardens, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B92
- Carriage Entrance, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B93
- Central Hall, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B96
- Small Dining Room, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B98
- Large Dining Room (South Wall), Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B99
- George and Martha's Bedroom, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B100
- Evolution of Mount Vernon, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B101
- Washington Family Savage Portrait, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B103
- Tea Room Mt.Vernon Trolley Station c. 1930, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B104
- Slave Quarters, Mount Vernon, VA, Undated; Mt.Vernon-B105
- Pearson House, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B1
- Pearson House, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B2
- Pearson House from Railroad Tracks, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B3
- Pearson House, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B4
- Pearson House, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B5
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B6
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B7
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B8
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B9
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B10
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B11
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B12
- Pearson's Store, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B13
- Pearson's Store - interior, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B14
- Pearson's Store - interior, Newington, VA, 1987 May; Newington-B15
- Blacksmith at Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1968 June; Occu-Blac-2
- Blacksmith at Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1968 June; Occu-Blac-3
- Carding wool at Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1968 June; Occu-Card-1
- Fairfax Herald Printing Press 1882, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Occu-Prin-1
- Spinning at Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1968 June; Occu-Spin-2
- Ossian Hall on Seal Of Fire Department, Annadale, VA, Undated; Ossian-Hall-B1
- Uncle Tom Bushrod (1889-1901) - Gum Springs, 1980 February; People-B1
- Clara Barton, Undated; People-B2
- Uncle Tom Bushrod-Gum Springs, 1980 February; People-B2
- Thomas Culpeper (2nd Lord) Link to Fairfax, Undated; People-B3
- Bushrod Washington - Gum Springs, Undated; People-B3
- Charles Drew - Gum Springs, 1988 February; People-B4
- Will Holland August 1932 - Gum Springs, 1980 February; People-B5
- Old West Ford - Gum Springs, 1980 January; People-B6
- Edon Hammond- Gum Springs, 1980 February; People-B7
- Edon Hammond- Gum Springs, 1980 February; People-B8
- Thomas 6th Lord Fairfax, Undated; People-B8
- Ann M. Fitzhugh c. 1874, Undated; People-B8
- Gantt Child at Walney (1906), 1980 January; People-B9
- Dr. Drew - Gum Springs, Undated; People-B9
- Cal Ferguson in Gum Springs, 1988 February; People-B10
- Gantt Child at Walney (1906), Undated; People-B10
- George Ford - Gum Springs, Undated; People-B11
- Jacob Haight, Undated; People-B11
- Ham Gray - Gum Springs, 1980 January; People-B12
- Arthur Machen, 1980 January; People-B13
- Ham Gray - Gum Springs, 1980 January; People-B13
- West Ford - Gum Springs, 1980 June; People-B14
- Arthur Machen, 1940s; People-B14
- Calvin in Front Of House - Gum Springs, 1980 June; People-B15
- Caroline Machen, 1980 June; People-B15
- Caroline Machen, 1980 June; People-B16
- L.H. Machen, 1980 June; People-B17
- L.H. Machen, 1980 June; People-B18
- L.H. Machen, 1980 June; People-B19
- L.H. Machen, 1980 June; People-B20
- Thomas Machen, 1980 June; People-B21
- Thomas Machen, Undated; People-B22
- George and Anne Eilbeck Mason, Undated; People-B23
- George and Anne Eilbeck Mason, Undated; People-B24
- Mosby- 3rd From Left At Fairfax County Court House, Fairfax, VA, Undated; People-B27
- Mosby- 3rd From Left At Fairfax County Court House, Fairfax, VA, Undated; People-B28
- Mount Vernon Ladies, Undated; People-B29
- Mount Vernon Ladies, 1980 August; People-B31
- Mount Vernon Ladies, 1980 August; People-B33
- Mount Vernon Ladies, 1980 August; People-B34
- Bryan Fairfax, Undated; People-B40
- Bryan Fairfax, Undated; People-B41
- Katherne, Lady Fairfax, Undated; People-B42